<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task
  PUBLIC '-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN'
  'dtd1.2/technicalContent/dtd/task.dtd'>
<!-- This file is part of the DITA Open Toolkit project hosted on 
     Sourceforge.net. See the accompanying license.txt file for 
     applicable licenses.-->
<!-- (C) Copyright IBM Corporation 2001, 2005. All Rights Reserved.
 *-->
<task id="task-inspect" xml:lang="en-us">
  <title>Inspect the transmitter</title>
  <shortdesc>Record details of the M800 meter's condition as received.</shortdesc>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <p>Use SalesLogix to record the condition of the customer’s equipment as received.  This 
        protects Mettler-Toledo from claims that customer equipment became damaged while in the 
        Mettler-Toledo facility for service.</p>
    </context>
    <steps>
      <stepsection>To inspect the meter:</stepsection>
      <step>
        <cmd>Log into SalesLogix and open the RMA number listed on the paperwork.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Inspect the enclosure of the M800 meter and check the appearance 
          of the front panel, looking for any visible damage.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Use the Phillips-head screwdriver to loosen the 4 screws on the front 
          panel to allow the top to lift open.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Inspect the visible boards and connectors.  Look for any broken or 
          damaged connectors, cracked surfaces, or exposed wires.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>If the customer did not send a usable power cord, attach one.  Power 
          the M800 and watch to make sure it turns on and progresses through the start-up 
          screens until the measurement screen displays.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>If the customer sent a patch cord, disconnect the leads by pushing the 
          orange spring clips with the small flat-head screwdriver one at a time while pulling 
          gently on each lead.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Record the details of any observed damage in SalesLogix.  If the M800 
          looks to be in good condition, put in the notes that the equipment looks fine.</cmd>
      </step>
    </steps>
  </taskbody>
  <related-links>
    <link format="dita" href="concept-purpose.xml" type="concept"/>
  </related-links>
</task>
